Benny Hassan, Full Stack Developer

Bennyh960@gmail.com

Phone: 052-4874600





Chemical Engineer (B.sc) in the past and Full Stack developer in the present. Motivated with high learning abilities, self-taught, and very friendly. Skilled in Front-End and Back-End technologies. Experience in process design, development, and project management.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp - AppelSeeds. (2022-2022)

- ❖ Intensive 6-months, 720 hours training program that encourages self-led.
- learning and group projects that simulate real-world development teams including Git workflow.
- Learning and applying front-end skills such as **HTML**, **CSS**, **JavaScript**.
- React and back-end skills such as **Node.js** and **MongoDB** database.
- ❖ Portfolio including plenty of coding projects. (Git, Demo)
- **Python** self-learn with a 2D game project from the Pygame library.

B.Sc in Chemical Engineering, SCE Ashdod (2011-2015)

Graduated with excellence (GPA 93).

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Developer, Dealigence (Internship) (2022-)

- Developing "Connection Assessment" API, a product that aims to evaluate connections strength between entities stored in DB using Postgres(SQL).
- Design of the required tables and their relationships (one-to-many, many-to-many, polymorphic association).
- * Retrieve data using scrapers, Parse it and load into the database (NodeJS, Puppeteer, Scrape-it, Sequelize ORM).
- Building complex queries focusing on efficiency (indexing, window function).

Process Engineer, Intel (2018-2021)

- ❖ Tool owner of production machines, responsible for tool performance, data, writing work plans, troubleshooting and Validation.
- Project management to improve Tool availability and quality performance.

Process Engineer, Merck (2015-2018)

- Design and develop technological production processes, problem-solving and improving product quality.
- Pilots operation, process improvement, and writing work plans.

Languages: Hebrew native speaker English Highly proficient

Skills: Analytical thinking, Curious, Interpersonal communication, Motivated, self-taught ...